<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dhruvik Donga</title>
    <link>https://dhruvik.cc/authors/dhruvik-donga/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dhruvik Donga</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dhruvik.cc/authors/dhruvik-donga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 Wrap up 🌈</title>
      <link>https://dhruvik.cc/posts/2023-wrap-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dhruvik.cc/posts/2023-wrap-up/</guid>
      <description>2023 Wrap Up: A Journey of Code, Beaches, and Resilience 🚀🏖️&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;As the pages of 2023 turn, let&amp;rsquo;s go through a series of events—coding escapades, sun-soaked beaches, and the quiet battles fought behind the scenes. Inspired by the wrap-ups from Spotify, YouTube Music, Reddit, and more, let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the major events that shaped 2023.&#xA;1. Miniwordgames.com Launch: 🚀&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Embarking on a coding journey, the dilemma of &amp;ldquo;what to build&amp;rdquo; led to the birth of miniwordgames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimplySocket</title>
      <link>https://dhruvik.cc/projects/simplysocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dhruvik.cc/projects/simplysocket/</guid>
      <description>Golang WebSocket Package for Real-time Messaging in Words Battle Game&#xA;This open-source Golang package leverages the power of Gorilla WebSocket to facilitate seamless communication within a Words Battle Game. Serving as a comprehensive wrapper, it efficiently manages clients, rooms, and messages. The package is designed to handle dynamic events, such as the addition or removal of clients from rooms, ensuring a smooth and interactive gaming experience. Dive into the codebase to explore its robust capabilities and enhance your real-time messaging infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini Word Games</title>
      <link>https://dhruvik.cc/projects/miniwordgames/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dhruvik.cc/projects/miniwordgames/</guid>
      <description>MiniWordGames is an engaging multiplayer word game that combines the thrill of real-time battles with the challenge of word creation. This project utilizes Golang for the backend server, Vue.js for the frontend application, WebSocket for real-time communication, and Docker for easy deployment. The game is hosted under the domain miniwordgames.com.&#xA;Tech Stack&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Features&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Real-time Battles: Challenge your friends or random opponents to fast-paced word battles.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
